<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
  <data noupdate="1">
    <record id="who_cadre_category_1" model="hrms.who.cadre.category">
      <field name="name">Health Professionals</field>
      <field name="description">Health professionals study, advise on or provide preventive, curative, rehabilitative and promotional health services based on an extensive body of theoretical and factual knowledge in
diagnosis and treatment of disease and other health problems. They may conduct research on human disorders and illnesses and ways of treating them, and supervise other workers.
The knowledge and skills required are usually obtained as the result of study at a higher educational institution in a health-related field for a period of 3–6 years leading to the award of
a first degree or higher qualification</field>
    </record>
    <record id="who_cadre_category_2" model="hrms.who.cadre.category">
      <field name="name">Health Associate Professionals</field>
      <field name="description">Health associate professionals perform technical and practical tasks to support diagnosis and treatment of illness, disease, injuries and impairments, and to support implementation of
health care, treatment and referral plans usually established by medical, nursing and other health professionals. Appropriate formal qualifications are often an essential requirement for
entry to these occupations; in some cases relevant work experience and prolonged on-the-job training may substitute for the formal education</field>
    </record>
    <record id="who_cadre_category_3" model="hrms.who.cadre.category">
      <field name="name">Personal Care Workers in Health Services</field>
      <field name="description">Personal care workers provide direct personal care services in health care and residential settings, assist with health care procedures, and perform a variety of other tasks of a simple
and routine nature for the provision of health services. These occupations typically require relatively advanced literacy and numeracy skills, a high level of manual dexterity, and good
interpersonal communication skills</field>
    </record>
    <record id="who_cadre_category_4" model="hrms.who.cadre.category">
      <field name="name">Health Management and Support Personnel</field>
      <field name="description">Health management and support personnel include a wide range of other types of health systems personnel, such as health service managers, health economists, health policy
lawyers, biomedical engineers, medical physicists, clinical psychologists, social workers, medical secretaries, ambulance drivers, building maintenance staff, and other general
management, professional, technical, administrative and support staff</field>
    </record>
    <record id="who_cadre_category_5" model="hrms.who.cadre.category">
      <field name="name">Health Service Provider Not Elsewhere Classified</field>
    </record>
  </data>
</odoo>